{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159370665","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159370665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 0949b511-ab25-4b8a-90a7-d09ba30930ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159377468","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159377468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 0949b511-ab25-4b8a-90a7-d09ba30930ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159382638","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159382637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 0949b511-ab25-4b8a-90a7-d09ba30930ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159387970","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159387969"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 0949b511-ab25-4b8a-90a7-d09ba30930ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159398039","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159398038"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159398837","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159398837"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159399915","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159399914"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOAMKA"," userResponse":" NILIPOAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159401084","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159401083"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATA"," userResponse":" NILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159401787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159401787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIAMSHA"," userResponse":" KIAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159402289","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159402289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" KINYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159402884","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159402883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159403140","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159403139"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159403905","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159403905"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159407646","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159407645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159408079","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159408079"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159408921","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159408921"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUTANA"," userResponse":" KUKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159409118","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159409118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159409801","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159409801"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159410150","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159410150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159410833","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159410832"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikimbia kwenda kukutana na rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159414015","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159414014"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINDI"," userResponse":" PINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159415016","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159415016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOMPATA"," userResponse":" NILIPOMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159416042","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159416042"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159417207","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159417206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISAHAU"," userResponse":" TULISAHAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159418039","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159418039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159418427","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159418427"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pindi nilipompata Muthoni tulisahau kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159421430","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159421430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159421607","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159421607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159422421","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159422421"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159423547","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159423546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULICHEZA"," userResponse":" TULICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159424252","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159424251"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHEZO"," userResponse":" MICHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159425102","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159425102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159425664","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159425664"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159425814","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159425814"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159426344","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159426344"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulicheza michezo tofauti karibu na nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159429110","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159429110"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159429299","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159429299"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159429912","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159429911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159430671","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159430671"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159431278","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159431278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159431675","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159431674"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159432391","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159432391"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Muthoni tulifanya kila kitu pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159436481","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159436479"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIAHIDIANA"," userResponse":" TULIAHIDIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159437204","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159437204"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159437945","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159437944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159438512","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159438512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159439199","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159439198"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159439795","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159439795"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159440364","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159440364"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159441088","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159441087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUZU"," userResponse":" KUFUZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159441612","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159441612"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliahidiana kufanya bidii katika masomo yetu na kufuzu vyema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEMA"," userResponse":" VYEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159444514","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159444514"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159444933","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159444932"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159445524","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159445523"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159446365","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159446365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159447213","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159447213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159448048","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159448047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini siku moja Muthoni hakufika shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159451012","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159451012"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIMAMA"," userResponse":" NILISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159451998","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159451998"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" MLANGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159453249","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159453248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" NIKIMSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159454514","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159454514"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159455775","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159455774"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisimama mlangoni nikimsubiri lakini hakufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159459041","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159459040"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159459478","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159459477"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159460475","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159460475"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPORUDI"," userResponse":" NILIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159461340","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159461340"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159462559","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159462558"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NILIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159462983","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159462983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159463658","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159463657"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159464506","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159464506"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159465291","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159465291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159465913","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159465912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159466345","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159466344"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159466740","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159466740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku ile niliporudi nyumbani nilimwambia mama kwamba Muthoni hakufika shuleni siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159470298","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159470297"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIENDELEA"," userResponse":" NILIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159470488","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159470488"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159471203","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159471202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159471664","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159471664"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159472645","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159472644"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159473588","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159473587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMKOSA"," userResponse":" NILIMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159474297","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159474297"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159475213","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159475213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliendelea na masomo yangu lakini nilimkosa Muthoni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159477906","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159477906"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159478827","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159478827"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOENDA"," userResponse":" NILIPOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159479718","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159479718"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159481107","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159481106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159481721","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159481720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159482362","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159482361"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159483044","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159483044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila nilipoenda shuleni nilimtafuta Muthoni kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159486225","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159486225"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159486998","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159486997"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159487633","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159487633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159488303","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159488303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159489397","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159489396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159490291","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159490290"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMKOSA"," userResponse":" NINAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159491048","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159491047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159491411","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159491411"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159492125","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159492125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159495008","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159495007"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159495109","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159495109"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159499935","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159499935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159506066","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159506066"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159510251","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159510250"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" b99c5126-f676-4299-84a0-daff939ccef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159520888","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159520888"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159521514","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159521513"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159521733","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159521733"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159522425","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159522424"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159523179","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159523179"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159523701","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159523701"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" MWETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159524803","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159524803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIJAA"," userResponse":" KILIJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159525737","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159525736"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159526126","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159526125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159526583","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159526583"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159526794","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159526794"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159527509","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159527508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159529808","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159529808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159530248","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159530247"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159531031","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159531031"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159531935","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159531935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEJAZA"," userResponse":" ZIMEJAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159532794","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159532794"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159535315","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159535314"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159536140","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159536140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159536381","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159536380"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159537066","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159537066"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159537757","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159537757"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159537851","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159537851"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159538655","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159538655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPAKIA"," userResponse":" KUPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159541446","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159541446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159542376","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159542376"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" WALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159543117","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159543117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159544149","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159544148"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159544264","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159544264"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159545049","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159545049"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159545787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159545786"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159546995","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159546995"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" ZILIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159550279","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159550279"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159553081","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159553081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159555400","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159555400"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159556420","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159556419"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGHARIBI"," userResponse":" MAGHARIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159559342","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159559341"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" NILISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159560140","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159560140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159560915","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159560914"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIITA"," userResponse":" AKIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159561169","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159561167"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159561812","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159561812"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159564213","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159564213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159564678","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159564678"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159565176","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159565175"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159566264","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159566264"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYOHITAJI"," userResponse":" NILIYOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159567092","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159567092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159567609","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159567609"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159568323","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159568322"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAFIRI"," userResponse":" USAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159568788","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159568788"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159571494","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159571492"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159571646","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159571646"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159572130","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159572130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159572808","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159572808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159573463","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159573463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159574117","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159574117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159574721","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159574721"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJAA"," userResponse":" KUJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159575567","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159575565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159575970","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159575970"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159576762","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159576761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159578511","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159578511"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," userResponse":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159579314","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159579314"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159580020","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159580020"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159582531","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159582531"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159582885","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159582885"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159583909","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159583909"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPAKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159584773","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159584773"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159585502","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159585502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159585637","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159585637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159586147","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159586147"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159588604","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159588604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159589642","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159589642"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIWEKA"," userResponse":" WALIIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159590207","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159590207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159590971","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159590968"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159591097","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159591096"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159591434","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159591434"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159594699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159594698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159595293","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159595293"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPYA"," userResponse":" WAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159596066","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159596066"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" WALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159596569","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159596569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKETI"," userResponse":" TIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159597223","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159597223"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159597924","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159597924"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159598911","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159598911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159599507","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159599507"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159599717","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159599716"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159600353","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159600353"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAA"," userResponse":" KUKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159603006","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159603006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159603871","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159603870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159604130","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159604129"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159604738","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159604737"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159605397","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159605396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159607109","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159607108"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159607296","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159607296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159607921","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159607921"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159608291","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159608291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159608658","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159608658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159612328","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159612327"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" NILIPENYEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159612868","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159612868"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159613656","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159613655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAKAA"," userResponse":" NIKAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159614209","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159614208"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159614377","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159614377"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159615006","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159615006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159617312","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159617311"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159618150","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159618149"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKETI"," userResponse":" ALIYEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159618676","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159618675"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159619296","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159619296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159620175","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159620175"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHIKA"," userResponse":" ALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159620713","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159620712"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159620967","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159620966"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159621863","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159621862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PLASTIKI"," userResponse":" PLASTIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159622286","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159622285"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159622848","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159622847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159623533","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159623533"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159626059","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159626059"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAA"," userResponse":" ALIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159627033","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159627033"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159627968","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159627968"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159628761","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159628761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOTI"," userResponse":" KOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159629355","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159629355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKUU"," userResponse":" KUUKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159630102","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159630102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159631161","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159631161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONEKANA"," userResponse":" ALIONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159631569","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159631569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159631843","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159631842"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159632613","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159632612"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159636116","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159636116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NILIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159636751","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159636750"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159637212","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159637212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159638012","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159638011"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAMBUA"," userResponse":" KUTAMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159638729","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159638729"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159639808","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159639808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159640706","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159640705"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAONDOKA"," userResponse":" NAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159641584","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159641583"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159642361","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159642361"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159643150","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159643150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159643787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159643787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" AMBAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159644873","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159644872"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILELEWA"," userResponse":" NILILELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159647482","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159647482"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159648117","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159648117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAENDA"," userResponse":" NAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159648740","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159648740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159649199","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159649199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159649804","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159649804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159653213","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159653212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPAKIAJI"," userResponse":" UPAKIAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159653859","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159653859"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159655329","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159655329"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAMILIKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAMILIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159655933","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159655933"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159656616","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159656616"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159657233","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159657233"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWA"," userResponse":" WAKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159658175","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159658175"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKETI"," userResponse":" WAMEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159660919","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159660919"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159661804","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159661804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZIDI"," userResponse":" WALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159663081","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159663080"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUKUMANA"," userResponse":" KUSUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159664113","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159664113"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159664891","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159664890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159665510","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159665509"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159665676","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159665676"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159666298","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159666297"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159667016","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159667015"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159667526","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159667526"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUZE"," userResponse":" WAUZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159668141","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159668140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159668641","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159668641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159670814","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159670813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159671590","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159671590"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159672713","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159672712"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAJA"," userResponse":" ALITAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159672921","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159672921"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159673700","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159673699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159674543","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159674543"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159674862","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159674862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159675467","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159675467"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159676465","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159676465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159677222","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159677222"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159679743","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159679742"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANENO"," userResponse":" MANENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159680172","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159680171"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159681548","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159681546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," userResponse":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159684616","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159684616"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159684777","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159684777"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159685575","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159685575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159686905","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159686905"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINUNUA"," userResponse":" WALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159687699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159687699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159690316","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159690316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159691307","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159691306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKANUNUA"," userResponse":" WAKANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159692455","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159692455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAFUNAJI"," userResponse":" VITAFUNAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159693232","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159693232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159693661","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159693661"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159694283","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159694282"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159695181","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159695181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUNA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159697954","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159697954"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WASIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159698161","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159698161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159698730","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159698729"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FEDHA"," userResponse":" FEDHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159699405","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159699405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159700065","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159700065"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159701187","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159701186"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" WALITAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159701586","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159701585"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159704776","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159704776"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159705110","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159705110"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159706139","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159706138"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKATIZWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKATIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159706357","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159706357"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159706818","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159706818"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159707138","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159707138"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159707710","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159707710"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HONI"," userResponse":" HONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159708202","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159708202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159708756","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159708755"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159709623","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159709622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHARA"," userResponse":" ISHARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159710242","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159710241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159711205","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159711205"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159712088","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159712088"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159712959","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159712958"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159715820","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159715820"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159716724","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159716724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATAKA"," userResponse":" ALIWATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159717526","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159717526"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159718319","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159718319"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159718843","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159718843"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159718957","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159718957"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159719468","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159719468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159722646","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159722646"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159723895","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159723895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUKUMANA"," userResponse":" WALISUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159724588","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159724588"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159725752","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159725752"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159726205","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159726205"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159726445","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159726445"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159727181","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159727181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHUKA"," userResponse":" KUSHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159729640","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159729640"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159730309","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159730309"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159731727","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159731727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWARUDISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWARUDISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159732452","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159732452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159733312","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159733312"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASALIO"," userResponse":" MASALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159733562","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159733561"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159734014","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159734014"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159734505","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159734505"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159737000","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159737000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159737811","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159737811"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159738465","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159738465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUHUDI"," userResponse":" JUHUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159738699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159738698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159739338","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159739338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159740138","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159740138"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUZA"," userResponse":" KUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159740715","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159740715"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159741192","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159741192"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159744211","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159744211"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159745525","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159745525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" LILIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159746508","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159746508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUONI"," userResponse":" KITUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159747902","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159747902"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUNGULIA"," userResponse":" NILICHUNGULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159748715","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159748715"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159751809","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159751808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159752397","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159752397"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159753204","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159753204"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEWAHI"," userResponse":" NINGEWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159753817","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159753817"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159754615","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159754615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159755077","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159755077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159755693","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159755692"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159759081","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159759081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159760409","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159760409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" ILIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159761402","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159761402"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159762151","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159762150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159762984","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159762984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINGI"," userResponse":" JINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159763475","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159763475"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159763593","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159763592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159764159","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159764159"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159767037","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159767037"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYAFUMBA"," userResponse":" NILIYAFUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159767526","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159767525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159768006","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159768005"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159769306","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159769306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKINUIA"," userResponse":" NIKINUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159769986","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159769986"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159773217","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159773217"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159773825","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159773825"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWAZO"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159774346","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159774345"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159775411","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159775411"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIREJEA"," userResponse":" YALIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159776317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159776317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159778612","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159778611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159779812","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159779812"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159780629","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159780629"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUWA"," userResponse":" ATAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159781793","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159781792"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" SALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159784194","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159784194"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159785092","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159785092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159785850","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159785849"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159786875","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159786875"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATALETA"," userResponse":" WATALETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159787289","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159787289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159788133","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159788133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159790199","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159790199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159791112","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159791112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159791540","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159791540"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159792651","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159792651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" ATAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159793765","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159793765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159794236","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159794236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159794872","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159794872"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHE"," userResponse":" MICHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159794937","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159794937"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159795441","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159795441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159795996","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159795996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159799452","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159799449"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159800438","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159800438"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKARIRI"," userResponse":" NILIKARIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159801293","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159801292"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159801561","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159801561"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159802347","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159802347"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159803234","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159803234"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159804001","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159804001"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159804947","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159804946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159805398","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159805398"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159805926","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159805926"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159808492","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159808491"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159808941","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159808941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159809971","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159809970"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" NAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159810620","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159810620"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159811430","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159811429"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATWA"," userResponse":" NILIPATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159811617","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159811617"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159812401","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159812401"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159815234","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159815234"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159815473","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159815473"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159815812","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159815811"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159816416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159816416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159817629","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159817628"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" NILIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159817886","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159817885"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159818682","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159818682"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159818891","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159818891"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159819622","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159819621"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITA"," userResponse":" KUITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159820399","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159820399"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159821562","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159821562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKWENDA"," userResponse":" WALIOKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159822194","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159822194"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159822827","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159822827"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159823411","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159823411"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159826035","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159826034"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" NILICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159826513","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159826513"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159826943","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159826943"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159827723","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159827722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159828144","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159828143"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159829004","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159829003"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159829565","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159829565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159829645","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159829644"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159830103","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159830102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159833105","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159833105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159833199","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159833199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159834088","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159834087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159835000","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159835000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159835886","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159835883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAJAA"," userResponse":" LINAJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159836491","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159836491"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159838739","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159838738"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159839365","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159839364"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159840012","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159840012"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159840900","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159840900"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEANZA"," userResponse":" LINGEANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159841883","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159841882"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159841994","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159841994"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159842449","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159842448"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159843378","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159843378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHARIKI"," userResponse":" MASHARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159845788","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159845788"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159845922","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159845921"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159846566","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159846566"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANA"," userResponse":" MAANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159847078","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159847077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159847793","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159847792"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159848623","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159848623"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159849207","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159849207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159849858","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159849857"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159850742","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159850741"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159851562","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159851562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159851797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159851796"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159852699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159852699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159855215","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159855214"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159855317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159855317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Y.rand.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159861508","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159861508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159867479","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159867478"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159872040","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159872039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 61b8d897-ba78-42e5-9409-ca1e0085d583"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159882486","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159882486"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159883321","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159883320"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159884039","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159884039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159884258","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159884258"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159884816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159884816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159885627","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159885626"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159886005","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159886005"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159886690","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159886690"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159889249","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159889249"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159889446","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159889445"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159890104","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159890104"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159890759","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159890759"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159891404","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159891403"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159892007","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159892007"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKA"," userResponse":" KICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159892224","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159892223"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159893119","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159893119"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAHARI"," userResponse":" KALAHARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159896317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159896317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159896940","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159896939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159897732","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159897732"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159898372","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159898372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159899398","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159899398"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159899908","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159899908"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159900767","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159900767"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159901555","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159901554"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159902280","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159902280"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159903049","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159903048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159905502","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159905501"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159906385","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159906385"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159907241","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159907241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159907606","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159907606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159908087","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159908087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159908803","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159908802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159909242","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159909241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159910005","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159910005"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZINI"," userResponse":" ZIZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159912383","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159912383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159913151","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159913150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159913701","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159913701"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159914214","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159914213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159914721","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159914721"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159917153","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159917153"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENDA"," userResponse":" NENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159918299","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159918298"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAMTAFUTE"," userResponse":" UKAMTAFUTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159918627","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159918627"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159921569","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159921569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEZEEKA"," userResponse":" NIMEZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159922118","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159922118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159922766","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159922766"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" SIWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159923698","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159923698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUKIMU"," userResponse":" KUKUKIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159924147","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159924147"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159925334","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159925334"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159925795","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159925795"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159926648","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159926648"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159928688","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159928688"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159929400","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159929400"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159930059","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159930059"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159930885","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159930885"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159931515","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159931514"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159931711","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159931711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159932651","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159932651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159933097","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159933097"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159934003","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159934003"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159937366","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159937366"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159938243","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159938243"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159938721","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159938720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159939963","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159939963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOANGAZA"," userResponse":" KILICHOANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159940507","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159940507"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159940650","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159940650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159941184","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159941183"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159943947","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159943947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159945061","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159945061"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159945595","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159945595"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159948370","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159948370"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159949609","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159949609"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159950359","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159950359"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159951039","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159951039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGAZA"," userResponse":" MWANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159951875","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159951874"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159952726","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159952726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159955142","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159955141"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159955615","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159955615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159956118","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159956118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159956611","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159956611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159957244","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159957244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159960568","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159960568"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159960576","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159960576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159961051","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159961050"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159961814","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159961813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159962804","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159962804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIUELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159963461","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159963461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159963484","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159963484"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159966133","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159966133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159966464","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159966464"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159966638","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159966638"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159967526","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159967526"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159969912","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159969911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBONA"," userResponse":" MBONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159970159","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159970159"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKO"," userResponse":" UKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159971026","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159971026"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159971524","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159971524"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159973869","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159973868"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159974101","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159974101"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159974545","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159974544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159975289","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159975289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159975296","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159975296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159976131","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159976131"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJIBU"," userResponse":" ULIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159978520","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159978520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159979152","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159979152"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159980405","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159980405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINIACHA"," userResponse":" WALINIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159980985","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159980984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159981855","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159981854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159982668","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159982668"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHAMA"," userResponse":" WALIHAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159985573","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159985572"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUTAKA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159986554","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159986551"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIBEBA"," userResponse":" KUNIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159987458","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159987458"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" MAANAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159987874","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159987874"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159988048","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159988048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159988495","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159988495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159989013","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159989013"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159991913","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159991913"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159992747","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159992747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159993530","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159993530"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159993924","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159993924"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159994797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159994797"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159994808","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159994808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159995592","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159995592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159997939","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159997939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550159998984","data":{"timestamp":" 1550159998984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUBEBA"," userResponse":" NITAKUBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160002105","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160002105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUPELEKA"," userResponse":" NITAKUPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160002990","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160002990"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160003976","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160003975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUJULISHE"," userResponse":" NIKUJULISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160004296","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160004295"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160005071","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160005070"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160007688","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160007688"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160008525","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160008525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160009313","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160009312"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIBEBA"," userResponse":" NIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160012134","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160012133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160013379","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160013379"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USILALAMIKE"," userResponse":" USILALAMIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160013901","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160013901"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160014213","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160014212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160014896","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160014896"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160015759","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160015759"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVYOWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAVYOWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160016712","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160016712"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHIMILI"," userResponse":" KUHIMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160017378","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160017377"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160018274","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160018274"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160020809","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160020809"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160021498","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160021498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160022220","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160022220"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160022869","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160022869"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160023569","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160023569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160023952","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160023951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160024587","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160024587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160025199","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160025198"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160025810","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160025810"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160026756","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160026756"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160027422","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160027422"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160027887","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160027886"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160028574","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160028574"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160029011","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160029010"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160031589","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160031589"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160032431","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160032430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160032996","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160032996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160033192","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160033192"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160033678","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160033678"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160034211","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160034211"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160034915","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160034915"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160035511","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160035511"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160036293","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160036291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160038248","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160038248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160038944","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160038944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160039683","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160039682"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160040072","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160040072"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160040776","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160040776"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160043558","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160043557"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160044245","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160044244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160044964","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160044963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160045596","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160045595"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160046299","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160046299"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160046683","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160046682"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160047310","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160047310"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160047912","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160047912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160048496","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160048495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160049442","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160049442"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160050115","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160050114"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160050582","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160050581"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160051269","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160051269"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160051700","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160051700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160054326","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160054325"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160055161","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160055161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160055718","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160055717"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160055917","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160055917"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160056401","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160056400"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160056930","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160056929"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160057643","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160057643"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160058217","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160058217"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160058986","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160058985"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160061518","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160061518"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160062213","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160062212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160062958","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160062958"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160063344","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160063342"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160064030","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160064029"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160067511","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160067511"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160068116","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160068116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160068663","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160068663"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPYA"," userResponse":" MAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160069375","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160069375"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160069795","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160069794"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160070545","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160070544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160070739","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160070738"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160071104","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160071103"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160071715","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160071714"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGINE"," userResponse":" MENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160072528","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160072527"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160074875","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160074874"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160075449","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160075444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160076278","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160076278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160077363","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160077362"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," userResponse":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160077912","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160077912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160078615","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160078615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160079222","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160079222"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160080275","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160080275"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160080999","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160080999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160081503","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160081502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160090448","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160090446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160090529","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160090529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.10.rand.say.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160098032","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160098031"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" c6b454b2-8cef-42bd-a38a-4ecc45c3a51b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160107833","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160107833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 837d91aa-4d30-4860-9240-cfae76878aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_0-8-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160113580","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160113579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 837d91aa-4d30-4860-9240-cfae76878aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160120253","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160120253"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 837d91aa-4d30-4860-9240-cfae76878aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-9-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160126424","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160126423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 837d91aa-4d30-4860-9240-cfae76878aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-9-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160132040","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160132040"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 837d91aa-4d30-4860-9240-cfae76878aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-9-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160146098","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160146098"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 837d91aa-4d30-4860-9240-cfae76878aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-9-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160146178","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160146178"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 912f0b87-f95d-4c80-b644-542c4ce96c36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATA"," userResponse":" NILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160150887","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160150887"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 912f0b87-f95d-4c80-b644-542c4ce96c36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi nilipoamka nilipata kiamsha kinywa changu kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160159647","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160159647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160160409","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160160409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160160606","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160160606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160161366","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160161366"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160164749","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160164749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" IMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160165512","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160165512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160169744","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160169744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160170670","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160170669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160171493","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160171492"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160175115","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160175115"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160175978","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160175978"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160179844","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160179844"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" MAZINGIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160180789","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160180789"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160184699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160184698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" YAMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160185920","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160185920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160189611","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160189611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160190530","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160190530"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160191351","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160191351"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160194945","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160194944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160195806","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160195805"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160199006","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160199006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160199077","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160199077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160204189","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160204189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160227654","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160227653"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3125527f-44aa-4f52-a121-f9f1e48f1eeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160227735","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160227735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3bb7a6ed-a83c-4b8b-aee5-636da6cded98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATEMBEZI"," userResponse":" MATEMBEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160239465","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160239465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3bb7a6ed-a83c-4b8b-aee5-636da6cded98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160251137","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160251136"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3bb7a6ed-a83c-4b8b-aee5-636da6cded98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160256376","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160256375"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3bb7a6ed-a83c-4b8b-aee5-636da6cded98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160305445","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160305445"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 3bb7a6ed-a83c-4b8b-aee5-636da6cded98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160305537","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160305536"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 54f5c453-1911-48c7-9e80-f0f55ce4afc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEENDA"," userResponse":" ZIMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160311286","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160311285"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 54f5c453-1911-48c7-9e80-f0f55ce4afc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160315571","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160315569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 54f5c453-1911-48c7-9e80-f0f55ce4afc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160338886","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160338885"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_B_D_Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160346439","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160346439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_B_D_Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160356949","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160356948"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_B_D_Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160363262","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160363261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_L_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160369975","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160369975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_Z_M"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160377632","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160377632"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_Z_M"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160384339","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160384339"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_G_V"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160392043","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160392043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_G_V"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160402466","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160402466"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_G_V"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160408785","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160408785"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_M_Z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160416310","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160416309"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_M_Z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160423017","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160423017"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_Z_M"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160429696","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160429695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_S_N"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160436367","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160436367"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_Z_N"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160443854","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160443854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_Z_N"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160450506","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160450505"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_Z_P"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160457173","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160457173"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_I_Z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160466221","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160466221"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" f50443cb-7cda-41d1-b41b-450bb5db4d33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_U_I_Z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160499464","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160499464"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160522827","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160522827"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160546097","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160546097"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160585473","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160585473"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160620593","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160620593"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160620829","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160620829"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160629244","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160629244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160635744","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160635744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" e5f547cc-1d7f-4e61-9d79-c888a0f2f6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160642587","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160642587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 5b592f1c-d95a-4902-8fac-1b6271bc68a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160657383","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160657383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 5b592f1c-d95a-4902-8fac-1b6271bc68a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160657687","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160657687"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 5b592f1c-d95a-4902-8fac-1b6271bc68a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160657854","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160657854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 5b592f1c-d95a-4902-8fac-1b6271bc68a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160672835","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160672835"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 10a46708-0c6a-4cbd-a5dc-c3ae919c1cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160687033","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160687032"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 10a46708-0c6a-4cbd-a5dc-c3ae919c1cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160689623","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160689623"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 10a46708-0c6a-4cbd-a5dc-c3ae919c1cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160689783","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160689783"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 10a46708-0c6a-4cbd-a5dc-c3ae919c1cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160696669","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160696669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 6d422428-96b0-4082-bc44-a473ce1e7734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160711695","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160711695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 6d422428-96b0-4082-bc44-a473ce1e7734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160714286","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160714286"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 6d422428-96b0-4082-bc44-a473ce1e7734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160714477","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160714477"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 6d422428-96b0-4082-bc44-a473ce1e7734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160755939","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160755939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" bbaae129-1ff6-4bbb-a779-e527979cf5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160757004","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160757004"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" bbaae129-1ff6-4bbb-a779-e527979cf5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160759482","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160759482"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" bbaae129-1ff6-4bbb-a779-e527979cf5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160759740","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160759740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" bbaae129-1ff6-4bbb-a779-e527979cf5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160772456","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160772455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160773511","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160773511"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160777160","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160777160"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160778214","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160778214"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160792028","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160792028"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160793126","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160793126"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160797907","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160797907"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550160798950","data":{"timestamp":" 1550160798949"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_184921"," gameId":" 9b3c58ae-f881-4cc7-aa47-ced1c3600aa1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}